A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - The Northeast-Midwest Institute (08450027), 1983 October 01-1984 June 30 (Reel R4991)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE DISPLACED WORKER PROBLEM
  - The Northeast-Midwest Institute (08500259), 1984 December 01-1988 March 31 (Reel R5390)
    SUPPORT FOR POLICY RESEARCH PROGRAM ON GROUNDWATER CONTAMINATION
    $266,000.00;$266,000.00
    Butcher, James E.
    Northeastern States; Middle West
  - The Northeast-Midwest Institute (08650452), 1986 April 01-1987 March 31 (Reel R4977)
    STUDY OF U.S. EMPLOYMENT SERVICE AND ITS ROLE IN A NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT AND TRAINING SYSTEM
    Arnold, David D.;Berlin, Gordon
  - The Northeast-Midwest Institute (08950669), 1989 May 01-1990 December 31 (Reel R6049)
    SUPPORT FOR POLICY GUIDE TO SUCCESSFUL PROGRAM DESIGNS FOR SERVING DISLOCATED WORKERS
    Arnold, David D.;Lanigan, John
  - The Northeast-Midwest Institute (09100306), 1990 November 01-1992 January 31 (Reel R6288)
    PREPARATION OF A REPORT ON THE ROLE OF PUBLIC UTILITIES IN U.S. RURAL ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT
    Rural Poverty & Resources Program [RPR];Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ]
    Arnold, David D.;Page, Chris B.
  - The Northside Preservation Commission (08300633), 1983 July 01-1990 February 28 (Reel R6301)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF GENERAL OPERATING COSTS AND OF HOUSING DEVELOPMENT ACTIVITIES
    Saint Louis (Mo.)
  - The North-South Institute (09101234), 1991 June 01-1996 February 29 (Reel R6951)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT ON "THE MULTILATERAL DEVELOPMENT BANKS BEYOND THE DEBT CRISIS"
    International Affairs Program [IA];Developing Country Programs [DCP]
    $100,000.00;$86,652.00
    Geithner, Peter F.;Gerhart, John D.;Ispahani, Mahnaz Z.;Trebat, Thomas J.
  - The North-South Institute (10000562), 2000 February 01-2005 March 31 (Reel R9200)
    SUPPORT FOR A PROGRAM OF ACTION-ORIENTED RESEARCH, CONFERENCES, AND PUBLICATIONS ON THE DEBT FINANCING PROBLEMS OF HIGHLY INDEBTED POOR COUNTRIES AND EMERGING MARKET NATIONS
    Human Rights;Governance and Civil Society
    $253,000.00;$253,000.00
    Canada; Global; Developing Countries; International economic relations--Global; Debts, External
  - The Norwegian Nobel Institute (05500023), 1954 November 29-1955 November 28 (Reel R0495)
    INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE IN JUNE 1955 TO DISCUSS WESTERN DEMOCRACIES AND WORLD PROBLEM
    $50,000.00;$33,445.05
  - The Nova Institute, Incorporated (08050207), 1980 January 01-1981 December 31 (Reel R2870)
    FOR A STUDY OF COMMUNITY BOARDS IN CITY GOVERNMENT
  - The Nucleus for Black Studies (09550832), 1995 April 01-1997 April 30 (Reel R7775)
    TEACHER TRAINING AND LEGAL ASSISTANCE FOR AFRICAN BRAZILIANS
    $75,000.00;$74,995.25
    Brooke, Nigel P.;Telles, Edward Eric
  - The Nucleus for Black Studies (09701865), 1997 July 01-2001 June 30 (Reel R8685)
    TEACHING MATERIALS AND LEGAL ASSISTANCE FOR AFRICAN BRAZILIANS
    $283,700.00;$283,700.00
    Brooke, Nigel P.;Dora, Denise Dourado
  - The Nucleus for Black Studies (09801822), 1998 August 01-2000 October 31 (Reel R8273)
    ANTI-RACIST LEGAL TRAINING FOR LAW STUDENTS
    Brazil (Rio de Janeiro);Human Rights
    $75,000.00;$74,998.36
    Dora, Denise Dourado;Jenkins, Alan
    Brazil; Law students--Brazil; Blacks -- Brazil -- Study and teaching; Race relations; Race discrimination--Law and legislation--Study and teaching
  - The Nucleus for Black Studies (10101699), 2001 May 01-2003 April 30; The Nucleus for Black Studies (Reel R9045)
    For programs to combat discrimination and advance the rights of southern Brazil's Afro-Brazilian population
    Brazil; Human rights advocacy -- Brazil; Race Discrimination--Brazil; Blacks -- Brazil -- Legal status, laws, etc..
  - The Nucleus for Black Studies (10151535), 2001 June 01-2002 May 31 (Reel R8851)
    Seminar in the Southern region of Brazil in preparation for the UN Conference Against Racism, Racial Discrimination, Xenophobia and Related Intolerance
    Dora, Denise Dourado
    Brazil; Race relations--Brazil; Intergroup relations -- Brazil; Blacks -- Brazil
  - The Nucleus for Black Studies (10351754), 2003 August 01-2005 July 31 (Reel R9102)
    To establish a national coalition of legal professionals and organizations against racism in Brazil and set up a women's rights program
    Leal, Ondina Fachel;Dora, Denise Dourado;Toni, Ana
  - The Oahu Development Conference (06400152), 1964 January 24-1965 January 23 (Reel R0162)
    SEMINARS FOR COMMUNITY LEADERSHIP GROUPS ON PLANNING AND RENEWAL ISSUES CONFRONTING HONOLULU
  - The Obafemi Awolowo Foundation (09701545), 1997 August 01-2002 December 31 (Reel R8999)
    SUPPORT TO CARRY OUT A STUDY OF PRIVATE FOUNDATIONS AND ENCOURAGE CORPORATE PHILANTHROPY IN NIGERIA
    $190,000.00;$140,447.53
    Aidoo, Akwasi;Odaga, Adhiambo P.
  - The Obafemi Awolowo Foundation (09750413), 1996 November 01-1998 December 31 (Reel R7890)
    SUPPORT FOR NGO PARTICIPATION AT A MICROCREDIT SUMMIT AND TO ENCOURAGE PRIVATE SECTOR INVOLVEMENT IN MICROCREDIT PGMS. IN NIGERIA
    Odaga, Adhiambo P.
  - The Oceanic Foundation (07000460), 1970 June 01-1971 November 30 (Reel R1211)
    GENERAL SUPPORT OF THE OCEANIC INSTITUTE
    $185,000.00;$149,295.00
    Felling, William E.
  - The Ockenden Venture (09051265), 1990 July 01-1991 October 01 (Reel R6582, Reel R7252)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF A LOCAL FORESTRY AND AGRICULTURAL INTENSIFICATION AND COTTAGE INDUSTRY PROGRAM, BY THAI-LAO MOUNTAIN COMMUNITIES
    $26,700.00;$26,700.00
    Thomas, David E.
    Thailand
  - The Ohio Academy Of Science (07850630), 1978 August 01-1979 January 31 (Reel R3367)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF SCHOLARLY EXCHANGE VISTS OF AMERICAN AND CHINESE GEOGRAPHERS
    $19,000.00;$19,000.00
    Balaran, Paul;Geithner, Peter F.
    China; United States
  - The Ohio College Association, Inc. (08050016), 1980 January 01-1981 December 31 (Reel R2872)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF COOPERATIVE STATEWIDE EFFORT TO ENHANCE INTERNATIONAL PROGRAMS AND INCREASE ENROLLMENT OF INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS
    Ohio
  - The Ohio Historical Society (09101058), 1991 August 01-1992 July 31 (Reel R6283)
    United States; Ohio
  - The Ohio Historical Society (09351000), 1993 July 01-1994 November 15 (Reel R6891)
  - The Ohio Historical Society (09351314), 1993 September 01-1996 February 29 (Reel R7498)
    PLANNING AND ORGANIZATIONAL DEVELOPMENT SUPPORT FOR THE AFRICAN AMERICAN MUSEUMS ASSOCIATION
  - The Ohio State University (05600327), 1956 September 12-1957 September 11 (Reel R0089)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND ADMINISTRATION 1956-57
    $11,796.00;$11,796.00
  - The Ohio State University (05700234), 1957 May 24-1957 May 23 (Reel R0090)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND ADMINISTRATION 1957-58
    $6,930.00;$6,930.00
  - The Ohio State University (05800227), 1958 June 09-1959 June 08 (Reel R0094)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND ADMINISTRATION 1958-1959
    $4,150.00;$4,150.00
  - The Ohio State University (05900285), 1959 June 10-1960 June 09 (Reel R0121)
    FACULTY STUDY FELLOWSHIP
    $9,010.00;$9,010.00
  - The Ohio State University (05900310), 1959 June 18-1960 June 17 (Reel R0098)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND ADMINISTRATION 1959-60
    $5,540.00;$5,540.00
  - The Ohio State University (05900425), 1959 August 13-1960 August 12 (Reel R0121)
    INSTITUTE OF BASIC MATHEMATICS FOR APPLICATION TO BUSINESS
    $22,054.00;$22,054.00
  - The Ohio State University (06000385), 1960 August 04-1961 August 03 (Reel R0102)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND ADMINISTRATION 1960-1961
    $11,338.00;$11,245.00
  - The Ohio State University (06100063), 1961 January 10-1962 January 09 (Reel R0252)
    PREPARATION OF A SET OF PROJECTIONS OF COLLEGE AND UNIVERSITY ENROLLMENTS
    $3,775.00;$3,737.67
  - The Ohio State University (06100278), 1961 July 28-1964 February 25 (Reel R0047)
    RESEARCH AWARDS FOR DEVELOPMENT OF NEW CONCEPTS AND PRACTICES OF DELINQUENCY PREVENTION AND CONTROL
    $7,164.00;$7,164.00
  - The Ohio State University (06200061), 1962 January 31-1970 June 30 (Reel R3079)
    FORGIVABLE LOANS FOR PREDOCTORAL STUDENTS INTENDING TO BECOME ENGINEERING TEACHERS
    Borgmann, Carl W. (Carl Williams)
  - The Ohio State University (06300113), 1963 January 16-1968 January 15 (Reel R1030)
    PROGRAM OF LEGISLATIVE INTERNSHIPS FOR GRADUATE STUDENTS OF OHIO COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES
    $105,000.00;$105,000.00
  - The Ohio State University (06400417), 1964 July 23-1971 July 31 (Reel R2200, Reel R2201, Reel R5611)
    TEACHING AND RESEARCH IN AGRICULTURAL ENGINEERING AT PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY IN INDIA
    $1,003,560.00;$1,003,560.00
    Erf, Herbert A.
  - The Ohio State University (06500176), 1965 April 16-1971 June 30 (Reel R1521)
    DEVELOPMENT OF AN INDUSTRY-RELATED MASTERS LEVEL PROGRAM IN DESIGN IN METALLURGICAL ENGINEERING
  - The Ohio State University (06700330), 1967 June 29-1969 June 28 (Reel R1881)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION AND ECONOMICS, 1967-68
    $6,180.00;$6,180.00
    Adkins, Ann
  - The Ohio State University (06800598), 1968 June 28-1969 June 27 (Reel R2241)
    FACULTY RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMICS, POLITICAL SCIENCE AND SOCIOLOGY, 1968-69
    $17,468.00;$17,429.00
  - The Ohio State University (06900635), 1969 August 21-1975 September 15 (Reel R2311, Reel R2740)
    SUPPORT OF A PROGRAM TO PREPARE PRINCIPALS AND OTHER ADMINISTRATORS FOR SCHOOLS IN URBAN NEIGHBORHOODS
    $825,592.00;$825,592.00
  - The Ohio State University (07100253), 1971 September 01-1972 August 31 (Reel R1729)
    DISSERTATION FELLOWSHIPS IN ETHNIC STUDIES FOR PH. D. CANDIDATES
    $5,000.00;$4,288.18
    Scanlon, John J.
  - The Ohio State University (07500485), 1975 January 01-1980 December 31 (Reel R4243)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH IN REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY AND CONTRACEPTIVE DEVELOPMENT
    $114,900.00;$114,900.00
  - The Ohio State University (07550260), 1975 July 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R3608)
  - The Ohio State University Development Fund (05600042), 1956 January 20-1960 January 19 (Reel R0295)
    SUMMER PROGRAMS IN FOREIGN AREAS AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES
    $25,000.00;$22,966.01
  - The Ohio State University Research Foundation (05900426), 1959 August 13-1962 August 03 (Reel R0177)
    EXPERIMENTAL PROJECT IN EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION
    $116,000.00;$116,000.00
  - The Ohio State University Research Foundation (07300104), 1973 July 01-1975 December 31 (Reel R2359)
    STUDY OF SOCIAL CLASS AND SUBNATION
    $50,000.00;$47,396.57
    Ruof, Peter
    Belgium
  - The Ohio State University Research Foundation (09951655), 1999 September 01-2000 December 31 (Reel R8669)
    SUPPORT TO MAP AND REVIEW THE POLICYMAKING INFLUENCE OF SERVICE ORGANIZATIONS AND TRADE ASSOCIATIONS SERVING THE NONPROFIT AND COMMERCIAL ARTS SECTORS
    United States; Arts -- United States; Arts surveys -- United States
  - The One To One Partnership, Inc. (09751932), 1997 September 01-1998 August 31 (Reel R9040)
    SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF MATERIALS TO ASSIST THE AFRICAN AMERICAN FAITH COMMUNITY TO IMPLEMENT MENTORING PROGRAMS FOR YOUTH
  - The Ontario Institute For Studies In Education (06700115), 1966 September 01-1967 November 30 (Reel R1854, Reel R1855)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR CURRICULUM STUDIES IN MATHEMATICS, READING ANDSCIENCES
    $175,803.06;$175,803.06
  - The Ontario Institute for Studies in Education (08050271), 1979 October 11-1980 April 10 (Reel R2547)
    PROMOTIONAL SUPPORT FOR THE JOURNAL, "RESOURCES FOR FEMINIST RESEARCH"
    $12,832.00;$12,832.00
  - The Ontario Institute for Studies in Education (08150234), 1981 January 01-1984 October 31 (Reel R4626)
    STUDY OF TEACHING PRACTICES AND CLASSROOM ENVIRONMENT AS THEY AFFECT LEARNING IN MATHEMATICS AND SCIENCE IN FIFTEEN COUNTRIES
    $24,500.00;$24,500.00
  - The Open Lands Project (06900688), 1969 September 01-1972 August 31 (Reel R1449)
    GENERAL SUPPORT TO STRENGTHEN CITIZEN EFFORTS ORGANIZED TO ASSIST MUNICIPAL GOVERNMENTS SHAPE & IMPLEMENT PARK & OPEN SPACE PLANNING
    Illinois
  - The Open Museum Association (OMA) (10051212), 2000 June 01-2001 March 31 (Reel R8957)
    TO SUPPORT THE PARTICIPATION OF OMA IN CONTEMPORARY ART EXHIBITIONS IN SIX CITIES, AND THE ORGANIZATION OF WORKSHOPS FOR SIBERIAN MUSEUMS
    Russia; Art--Exhibitions--Russia (Federation); Art museums--Russia (Federation)
  - The Open School (08550929), 1985 October 23-1988 March 31 (Reel R5549)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR CLASSES AND WORKSHOPS ON THE ARTS FOR BLACK SOUTH AFRICAN SCHOOL CHILDREN
  - The Open University (07300149), 1972 November 10-1976 November 09 (Reel R2255, Reel R2328)
    PROJECT TO DEVELOP & DISSEMINATE INFORMATION ON NEW METHODS OF STUDENT ASSESSMENT & STRONGER METHODS OF CURRICULUM DESIGN
    Education and Public Policy;European and International Affairs
    $116,220.00;$116,220.00
    Meade, Edward J.;Ruof, Peter
  - The Open University (07950468), 1979 March 01-1980 February 28 (Reel R2265)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF "THE OPEN UNIVERSITY CONFERENCE ON THE EDUCATION OF ADULTS AT A DISTANCE"
    Bischoff, Irma E.;Crossland, Fred E. (Fred Eugene);Sutton, Francis X. (Francis Xavier)
  - The Open University (08850560), 1988 February 01-1990 July 31 (Reel R5966, Reel R6162)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT ENTITLED: DEVELOPING THE GANGES: A STUDY OF THE LOST OPPORTUNITY OF 1985-87
    India, Nepal and Sri Lanka (New Delhi);Bangladesh [ASIA/BA]
    $24,600.00;$24,600.00
    Offenheiser, Jr., Raymond C.;Shad, Shekhar
    South Asia
  - The Open University (10351167), 2003 July 01-2004 June 30 (Reel R9204)
    For the Center for Higher Education Research and Information to complete research and comparative analysis on the role of universities in the transformation of societies
    Education, Sexuality, Religion
    Balan, Jorge
  - The Opera Association Of New Mexico (06200234), 1962 April 17-1962 October 16 (Reel R0944)
    SYMPOSIUM FOR YOUNG COMPOSERS IN CONNECTION WITH A STRAVINSKY FESTIVAL IN SANTA FE
    $22,800.00;$21,377.30
  - The Opera Association Of New Mexico (06300536), 1963 September 30-1968 September 29 (Reel R2648)
    EXTENSION AND STIMULATION OF PROFESSIONAL CIVIC OPERATIC RESOURCES
  - The Opera Association Of New Mexico (06800144), 1968 January 29-1970 January 28 (Reel R2080)
    ASSISTANCE TOWARD THE COSTS OF NEW PRODUCTIONS DURING THE 1968 AND 1969 SEASONS
    D'Arms, Edward F.
  - The Opera Association Of New Mexico (07200078), 1971 October 01-1975 September 30 (Reel R1750)
    SUPPORT TO PROVIDE A CASH RESERVE TO IMPROVE AND STABILIZE THE ASSOCIATION'S FINANCIAL POSITION
    $747,955.00;$747,955.00
  - The Opera Association of New Mexico (08100569), 1980 October 01-1984 September 30 (Reel R4670)
    TO IMPROVE AND STABILIZE THE FINANCIAL POSITION
    $87,320.00;$87,320.00
  - The Opera Company Of Boston, Inc. (06600451), 1966 October 11-1968 October 10 (Reel R1802)
    STABILIZATION OF THE COMPANY'S PERFORMANCE ACTIVITIES
    $195,000.00;$195,000.00
  - The Opera Company Of Boston, Inc. (07100551), 1971 June 01-1976 May 31 (Reel R1733)
    SUPPORT TO PROVIDE CASH RESERVES TO IMPROVE AND STABILIZE THE FINANCIAL POSITION OF SELECTED PERFORMING ARTS ORGANIZATIONS
    $492,226.00;$492,226.00
  - The Orchestral Association (06600275), 1966 July 01-1976 June 30 (Reel R2977, Reel R4342)
  - The Oregon Community Foundation (08951343), 1989 September 01-1989 December 31 (Reel R6414)
    SUPPORT TO DESIGN COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT FUNDING COLLABORATIONS IN PORTLAND
    $21,500.00;$21,500.00
    Portland (Or.)
  - The Oregon Community Foundation (09000231), 1990 April 01-1993 March 31 (Reel R6470)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE REPLICATION OF THE CALIFORNIA CHILD CARE INITIATIVE IN OREGON
    $415,000.00;$415,000.00
    United States; Oregon
  - The Oregon Community Foundation (09000699), 1990 May 01-1998 June 30 (Reel R8174)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR THE NEIGHBORHOOD PARTNERSHIP FUND IN PORTLAND, OREGON
    $1,900,000.00;$1,900,000.00
    United States; Portland (Or.)
  - The Oregon Community Foundation (09200730), 1992 May 01-1993 April 30 (Reel R6475)
    SUPPORT TO DESIGN A REVOLVING LOAN FUND
  - The Oregon Community Foundation (09700942), 1997 April 01-2000 July 31 (Reel R8386)
    SUPPORT FOR THE 1997 COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT PARTNERSHIPS CONFERENCE
  - The Oregon Community Foundation (09900964), 1999 July 01-2000 June 30 (Reel R8691)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO HELP THE NEIGHBORHOOD PARTNERSHIP FUND PROMOTE COMPREHENSIVE COMMUNITY-BUILDING STRTEGIES STATEWIDE
    United States; Community development corporations -- United States; Community development -- Oregon; Rural development--Oregon
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (08850914), 1988 June 29-1990 June 28 (Reel R5927)
    SUPPORT THE COMPILATION OF A TIBETAN CULTURAL RESOURCES DATA BASE
    Tibet Autonomous Region (China) Autonomous Region (China)
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (09000492), 1991 March 14-1992 September 14 (Reel R5940)
    TO FACILITATE THE IMPLEMENTATION AND PUBLICATION OF THE TIBETAN CULTURAL RESOURCES DATABASE
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (09200700), 1992 May 01-1995 May 01 (Reel R6768)
    SUPPORT FOR THE TIBETAN ORAL HISTORY RECORDING PROJECT
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (09451200), 1994 August 01-1995 July 31 (Reel R7992)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PREPARATION OF A GUIDE TO NEW DIGITAL ARCHIVING TECHNOLOGIES
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (09600528), 1996 April 01-1999 March 31 (Reel R8298)
    SUPPORT FOR TIBETAN CULTURAL RESOURCES PROJECT
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (09751109), 1997 June 01-1997 October 01 (Reel R7348, Reel R7487)
    RESEARCH & DEVELOPMENT PHASE FOR A PROJECT TO DEVELOP MULTIMEDIA, EDUCATIONAL RESOURCES & PROMOTE CULTURAL PRESERVATION IN TIBET
    $35,485.00;$35,485.00
    Saich, Tony
  - The Orient Foundation (Seattle) (09800269), 1997 October 01-2000 September 30 (Reel R7379)
    SUPPORT FOR A CAPACITY BUILDING INITIATIVE IN NEW MEDIA TECHNOLOGIES
    $110,000.00;$110,000.00
    India; Mass media and art--India
  - The Other Economic Summit NA (09151425), 1991 August 01-1992 January 01 (Reel R6135)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR ORGANIZING COSTS AND FACILITATION OF MEXICAN PARTICIPATION AT THE ORGANIZATION'S FIRST ANNUAL SUMMIT CONFERENCE
    Collins, Norman R.;Sanchez, Raul M.
  - The Other Economic Summit NA (09251276), 1992 August 01-1993 January 01 (Reel R8874)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR CONFERENCE EXPENSES AND TRAVEL COSTS FOR MEXICAN AND CENTRAL AMERICAN PARTICIPATION
    Krasevac, Kimberly A.
    Mexico; Central America
  - The Other Theatre, Inc. (06800627), 1968 June 26-1971 August 31 (Reel R2176)
    SUPPORT OF PLAYWRIGHTS' PRODUCTION WORKSHOP
    $102,250.00;$102,250.00
  - The Other Theatre, Inc. (07950517), 1979 June 01-1979 August 31 (Reel R2403)
    EXPLORATION OF INNOVATIVE THEATER TECHNIQUES
    $8,000.00;$8,000.00
  - The Ouachita Baptist College (05600356), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel R0299)
    $188,000.00;$188,000.00
  - The Pace Association (06500181), 1965 April 23-1966 April 22 (Reel R1234)
    SUMMER PROGRAM OF EDUCATIONAL ENRICHMENT FOR STUDENTS HANDICAPPED BY CULTURAL AND EDUCATIONAL DEPRIVATION
    $50,000.00;$43,687.11
  - The Pace Association (06800565), 1968 July 01-1970 October 31 (Reel R2223, Reel R2224)
    EXPANSION OF THE HUMAN RELATIONS CURRICULUM PROJECT IN CLEVELAND SCHOOLS AND COMMUNITY ORGANIZATIONS
    $166,000.00;$166,000.00
    Sandberg, Donald F.
  - The Pacific Basin Institute (08900877), 1989 June 01-1992 May 31 (Reel R6292)
    PARTIAL FUNDING FOR A TELEVISION SERIES ON THE PACIFIC WORLD (008)
    Education & Culture Program [EC];US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP]
    $1,250,000.00;$1,250,000.00
    Stanley, Peter W.;Taylor, Andrea L.
    North Asia; SouthEast Asia; Pacific States
  - The Pacific Society of China (09550702), 1995 May 01-1997 April 30 (Reel R7704)
    SUPPORT FOR A NEW JOURNAL ON THE ECONOMICS, POLITICS AND CULTURE OF THE PACIFIC REGION
  - The Pacific Society of China (10150934), 2001 April 01-2003 March 31 (Reel R8974)
    Support for publication of "Pacific Journal"
    Watson, Andrew
    China; Area studies -- China
  - The Pakistan Academy For Rural Development (06400449), 1964 August 25-1965 August 24 (Reel R1613, Reel R1614, Reel R3993, Reel R5322)
    VISITOR HOUSING FACILITIES FOR THE ACADEMY FOR RURAL DEVELOPMENT AT COMILLA
    $20,000.00;$19,648.51
    Bunker, Samuel E.;Erf, Herbert A.
  - The Pakistan Academy For Rural Development (07400076), 1973 December 10-1976 June 30 (Reel R3453, Reel R3454, Reel R5110)
    CONSULTANTS, DOMESTIC AND FOREIGN TRAINING, EQUIPMENT AND LIBRARY MATERIALS FOR RURAL DEVELOPMENT
    $120,000.00;$43,536.90
    Collins, Norman R.;Jones, Sidney
  - The Pakistan Academy For Rural Development (07950513), 1979 May 31-1979 June 30 (Reel R3094, Reel R3904)
    ASSIST PARTICIPATION OF PROFESSOR GARTH JONES OF UNIV. OF ALASKA IN INTERNATIONAL SEMINAR AND WORKSHOP ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT
    $7,200.00;$7,200.00
    Collins, Norman R.;Geithner, Peter F.
  - The Pakistan Arts Council (07350458), 1972 November 14-1974 April 13 (Reel R1172, Reel R4286)
    RESEARCH IN CLASSICAL MUSLIM MUSIC
    Miller, Frank J.;Quinn, John A.
  - The Palestinian Ngo Network (09601053), 1996 June 01-2004 December 31 (Reel R9101)
    SUPPORT FOR A COALITION OF WEST BANK-GAZA NGOS
    $1,065,000.00;$1,065,000.00
    Azzam, Fatih Samih
    Gaza; West Bank
  - The Palmetto Conservation Foundation (09101129), 1991 August 01-1992 March 31 (Reel R6420)
    SUPPORT TO ASSESS POVERTY AND ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUES IN TOURISTIC REGIONS OF SOUTH CAROLINA
    Lipsky, Michael;Page, Chris B.
  - The Panos Institute (08800233), 1988 January 01-1989 December 31 (Reel R5954)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE INSTITUTE'S "TIES THAT BIND" PROJECT
  - The Panos Institute (08800898), 1988 August 22-1998 September 30 (Reel R8169)
    SUPPLEMENTAL SUPPORT FOR THEIR AIDS PROGRAMME, INCLUDING AN INDIGENOUS LANGUAGE AIDS INFORMATION PROJECT (010)
    Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Developing Country Programs [DCP];Reproductive Health And Population Program [RHP]
    $884,000.00;$884,000.00
    Muecke, Marjorie A.
  - The Panos Institute (08900837), 1989 July 01-1991 July 01 (Reel R6548)
    GENERAL SUPPORT OF THE INSTITUTE'S ACTIVITIES IN THE AMERICAS
    Forman, Shepard;Gaberman, Barry D.
    Canada; Latin America; Global; United States
  - The Panos Institute (08950531), 1988 December 01-1989 June 01 (Reel R5549, Reel R6521)
    SUPPORT FOR THE INTERNATIONAL PRESS SEMINAR ON "DEVELOPMENT COSTS OF CONFLICT IN SOUTHERN SUDAN," DECEMBER 1988
    Middle East and North Africa (Cairo);Eastern Africa (Nairobi)
    $15,372.00;$15,372.00
    Playfair, Emma
    Sudan
  - The Panos Institute (08950602), 1989 June 27-1990 June 27 (Reel R6009)
    SUPPORT FOR AN INTERNATIONAL CONSULTATION ON THE ROLE OF THE CHURCH IN ADDRESSING AIDS
    Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Developing Country Programs [DCP]
    Cuevas, Christina
    United States; Developing Countries
  - The Panos Institute (09000495), 1990 January 01-1992 January 01 (Reel R6323, Reel R8659)
    SUPPORT FOR AN ENVIRONMENTAL INTERNSHIP AND BACKSTOPPING OF BANGLADESHI ENVIRONMENTAL NGOS
    $42,233.00;$42,233.00
    Capistrano, Ana Doris
    Bangladesh
  - The Panos Institute (09001349), 1990 July 01-1991 July 01 (Reel R5760, Reel R5768, Reel R5873)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR STUDIES AND A CONFERENCE ON THE DEVELOPMENT OF THE INDEPENDENT PRESS IN FRANCOPHONE WEST AFRICA
    Hodges, Anthony D. C.
    Africa, West
  - The Panos Institute (09101389), 1991 July 01-1992 June 30 (Reel R6699)
    SUPPORT FOR ITS PROGRAM ON ENVIRONMENT, COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT AND RACE
  - The Panos Institute (09150954), 1991 June 18-1993 June 18 (Reel R6314)
    SUPPORT FOR AN AIDS PROGRAM IN TAMIL NADU (INDIA)